Guide to the Pittsburgh Zionist District Records, 1945-1965 AIS.1968.12
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Pittsburgh Zionist District Records
1945-1965
1955-1965
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Pittsburgh Zionist District
AIS.1968.12
40 Linear Feet (96 boxes, 6 oversize volumes)
The Pittsburgh Zionist District Records document the activities of the Pittsburgh chapter of the Zionist Organization of America between 1945 and 1965. The collection consists primarily of correspondence, campaign materials, publicity, committee materials andn reports, records of celebrations and dinners, fundraising and membership records, programs, and publications.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Mr. H.H. Kimel of the Pittsburgh Zionist District on June 28, 1968.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Previous Citation
Pittsburgh Zionist District Records, 1945-1965, AIS.1968.12, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Related Material
Farband-Labor Zionist Order Records, 1950-1970, AIS.1998.13, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Hadassah, Pittsburgh Chapter Records, 1917-1968, AIS.1968.13, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Histadrut Records, 1956-1990, AIS.2010.08, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
United Jewish Federation of Pittsburgh Records, 1912-1964, AIS.1997.24, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
History
The Pittsburgh Zionist District is the Pittsburgh chapter of the Zionist Organization of America (founded in 1897), the oldest American Zionist organization. Its mission is to "build support for Israel and strengthen the United States/Israel relationship through public education, the media and public activism," according to the Jewish Federation of Greater Pittsburgh. The Pittsburgh chapter was one of the earliest chapters and dates to 1938, if not earlier. While it used to cover a large geographical area, spanning from Pennsylvania to Ohio, West Virginia, and even parts of New York, currently, it is based only in Western Pennsylvania.
Scope and Content Notes
The Pittsburgh Zionist District Records include correspondence, memoranda, and papers of the Executive Directors and Presidents (1955-1965); minutes, correspondence, nominations of the Executive Board (1955-1965); committee reports; membership correspondence, mailings, lists (paid, unpaid, resigned), campaigns, membership Dues Book (partial: M-Z), 1945-1955; financial records-paid bills, dues, receipts, fund drives, Contributions Record Book, 1955-1965; meetings of conferences and conventions; social, cultural, political activities and developments; public relations; regional reports; photographs; local organization publications including Pittsburgh Zionist; miscellaneous publications from other Jewish groups; and memorabilia.
Arrangement
The records remain in their original order.
Associations; Societies; Memorabilia; Jews -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh -- History; Zionism -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Israel -- Politics and government -- 1948-1967; Kibbutzim; Pittsburgh (Pa.) -- Social conditions; Correspondence; Memorandums; Administrative records; Reports; Membership lists; Financial records; Photographs; Social action; Politics; Alija Chadascha (Political party); Flitman, A.; Bernstein, J. B.; Landes, Morris A.; Pittsburgh Zionist District; American Zionist Federation; Zionist Organization of America; American Christian Palestine Committee; United Jewish Federation of Pittsburgh; Young Zionist District (Pittsburgh, Pa.); B'nai Israel Congregation (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Jewish National Fund; American Zionist Council; Stahl, Irwin; Kimel, H. H.; Ilutovitch, Leon
- Membership M-O, 1945-1955 (Oversize 1)
- Membership P-R, 1945-1955 (Oversize 2)
- Membership Sa-Se, 1945-1955 (Oversize 3)
- Membership T-Z, 1945-1955 (Oversize 4)
- Record Book of Past Contributors (Oversize 5)
- Record Book of Contributors (Oversize 6)
- Congratulation Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Sympathy Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Dr. Landes Regular Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Henry Stern Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Dr. Landes Pending, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- H.H. Kimel. Pending, 1955-1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- H. Manzer. Pending, 1955-1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Dr. Landes. Personal Correspondence, 1955-1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Dr. Landes. Travel, 1955-1965 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Kimel, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Menzer, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Executive Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Officers, Regular, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Meetings, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Inquiries, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Board Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Board Minutes and Agendas, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Staff Letters, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- American Christian Palestine Committee, 1956-1959 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Program Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Regular Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Program Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- AZF Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Nominations Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Committees Regular, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Cultural Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Emergency Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Committee on Israel and Middle East, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Executive Committee Rending, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Executive committee Agendas, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Membership Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- List of All Mailings, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Mailings (Special Literature), 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Members, Mailing by Works, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Members Mailings to Workers, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- AZP Mailings to Prospects, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Paid Bills,- Jan., Feb., March, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- AZF. Unpaid, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Economic Horizons, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- U.J.F., 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Bonds, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Conferences, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- ZOA Convention, Washington D.C., June 16-20, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- ZOA Convention, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Annual Meeting, May 24, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Membership Report, Yellow Copy, 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Membership Lists, 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- AZF Records, 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Membership Resignations, 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Membership Data, 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Membership Reports, 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Telephone, 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Membership Campaigns, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Workers Lists, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Membership Kickoff, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Unassigned Lists, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Duplicate Workers Lists, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Unassigned Lists Duplicates, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 6-8)
- Membership, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Duplicate Workers Lists, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Unassigned Lists Duplicates, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Masters Membership Campaign, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Workers Lists, 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
- Danchek, 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Budget, 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Paid Bills, July, August, Sept., 1955 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Paid Bills- April, May, June, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 6-7)
- Paid Bills- April, May, June, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Paid Bills- July, August, September, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Paid Bills- October, November, December, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- AZF Seating, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Purim Dance, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 2-3)
- AZF Kickoff, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Shekel Camp, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 5-6)
- Israel Tours, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Music and Arts, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Travel Plans, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- NAC, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Publicity, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Public Relations, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Synagogue Relations, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Regional Reports, Aliquippa, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Regional Reports, Altoona, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Regional Reports, Beaver Falls, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Regional Reports, Brownsville, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Regional Reports, Butler, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Regional Reports, Canonsburg, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Regional Reports, Ellwood City, PA., New Castle, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Regional Reports, Erie, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Regional Reports, Farrell, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Regional Reports, Greensburg, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Regional Reports, Indiana, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Regional Reports, Jeannette, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Regional Reports, Johnstown, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Regional Reports, Kittanning, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Regional Reports, Latrobe, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Regional Reports, Mon Valley, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Regional Reports, New Kensington, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Regional Reports, Oil City, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Regional Reports, Sharon, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Regional Reports, Uniontown, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Regional Reports, Warren, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Regional Reports, Wheeling, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Regional Conference, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Conference Data, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Conference, Regular, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- AZF Data, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- AZF Region, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Key Leaders, Regular, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Finished Reports, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- NAC, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Education, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Regional Membership, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Regional Membership Reports, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Membership Data, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Membership Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Lists- Membership, Regional Key Leaders, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- K'far Silver- ZOA House Region, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- List of All Mailings, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- National Convention, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- New York Releases, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- World Zionist Affairs, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- AZF Data, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- AZF Miscellaneous, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Advance and Duplicate Payment, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Political Developments, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Israel News Service, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Israel Digest, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Political Developments, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 9-10)
- AZ Committee for Public Affairs, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Israel Information, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Education, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 13-14)
- Books Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Youth Committee Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- YZD Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Youth and Young Zionist, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Publications, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Bulletins, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Program Data, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Israel Fotofacts, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Photos, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Henry Stern Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Congratulations, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Condolence and Recovery, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- David Lowenthal Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Leon Ilutovich Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Dr. Marks Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Staff Letters, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- A Flitman, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- H. Kimel, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Bulletins, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- General, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 12-14)
- Board Pending, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Board Minutes and Agendas, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Food to Israel Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Board Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Nominations Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Standing Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Committee on Israel and Middle East, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Executive Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 22-23)
- Executive Committee Pending, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Emergency Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Cultural Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Membership Relations Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Membership Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
- Membership Mailing to Workers, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Membership Statistics, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Membership Checks, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Membership Data, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 6-7)
- Membership Billings, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Membership Lists, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Membership Billings by Workers, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Membership Campaign, 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 1-3)
- AZF Kickoff, 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- AZF Lists, 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Loan Record, 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Financial Reports, 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 7-8)
- Budget, 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Revolving Fund, 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 10-11)
- Paid Bills- January, February, March, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Paid Bills- July, August, September, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Paid Bills- April, May, June, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- U.J.F. (United Jewish Federation), 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Economic Investment Data Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Economic Horizons, 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Eastmont, 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Economic Folder, 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- American Zionist Fund Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- B.I.G. News (Bonds of Israel Government), 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Bonds, 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Spring Conference, 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Conferences, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
- Zionist Organization of America, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Annual Meeting, Hebrew Institute, May 28, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Program Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Purim Dance, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Program Data, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Board Dinner- June 27, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- American Zionist Fund Mailings to Workers, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- AZF Seating, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 10-11)
- Films, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Membership Victory Dinner, B'nai Israel, March 21, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Committee Reports, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Speakers, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- AZF Data, 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- AZF Program Book, 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Music and Arts Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Israel Tours, 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Department of Public Information, 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Interfaith, 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Radio, 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Publicity, 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- PZC Publicity, 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Editors and Newscasters, 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- World Zionist Affairs, 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Relations With and Reports from World and National Organizations, 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 6-7)
- Conference, Baldoc Hills Country Club, July 12, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Regional Conference, May 13, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Conference, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Committees, Regional, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Regional Conference, Gateway Plaza, June 9, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 5-6)
- Regional Conference, November 25, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Reports, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Key Leaders, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Kfar Silver- ZOA House Region, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Leadership Dinner, Regional, July 12, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Membership Reports, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Membership Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Officers, Regional, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Regional Conference Photos, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Regional Meetings, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Regions, Others, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Revolving Fund, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Henry Stern Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Paid Bills, Revolving Fund, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Paid Bills, Regular Account, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Bills Payable, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- S. Saul Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- S. Saul Pending, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Conferences, Regional, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- S. Saul Personal Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- AZF Regional, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- ZOA Regional, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Regional Reports, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- H. Kimel Pending, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Bradford Folder, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Advance and Duplicate Dues, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Duplicate Payment and Letters, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Membership, ZOA, Aliquippa, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Altoona, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Beaver Falls, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Brownsville, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Butler, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Canonsburg, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Erie, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Farrell, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Greensburg, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Indiana, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Jeannette, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Johnstown, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Kittanning, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Latrobe, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Ellwood City and New Castle, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- New Kensington, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Mon Valley, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Oil City, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Sharon, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Uniontown, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Vandergrift, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Washington, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Wheeling, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Warren, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Washington, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- American-Zionist Committee for Public Affairs, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- America-Israel Society, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Political Developments, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- National Education Council, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- New York Release, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Refugee, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Program and Education, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Israel Information, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Education, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Books Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Youth Committee Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Rabbis- Region, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Young Zionist District Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Young Zionist District, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Sports for Israel, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous Signature File, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Hebrew University, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Hospitalization, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Form Letters, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Brandeis, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Cuts, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- A. Flitman, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Leon Ilutovich Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- H.H. Kimel, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- David Lowenthal, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- American Zionist Fund Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- American Zionist Council Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Memoranda, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Executive Committee, Attendance at Meetings, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Executive Committee, Minutes of Meetings, April 1957- May 1958, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Board Decisions, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Executive Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Board of Directors Meeting Attendance, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Board Pending, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- 1957 Convention (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Executive Committee Agendas, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Board Minutes and Agendas, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Board Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Nominations Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Cultural Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Committees, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Program Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Members Transfers Miscellaneous, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Membership Mailings to Workers, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Membership Mailings by Workers, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Changes of Address, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Membership Lists, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Membership Billings, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Membership Lists, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Membership Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Membership Miscellaneous, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Membership Campaigns, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
- Membership Campaign Analysis, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Membership Kickoff, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Membership Campaign, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Membership- Miscellaneous, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Membership Campaign Victory Dinner, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Financial Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Financial Statements, October- September, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Budget, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Advance and Duplicate Dues, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Paid Bills, April, May, June, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Paid Bills, October, November, December, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Paid Bills, Miscellaneous, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- United Jewish Appeal, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- United Jewish Federation, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Jewish National Fund, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- AZF Meetings, Photos, Data, Lists of Committees, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Economic Horizons, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Bonds, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- AZF Mailings to Prospects, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Membership Campaigns, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- American Zionist Fund, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- AZF Unpaid Pledges, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Orientation Conference, May 23, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Conferences, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Convention- National, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- ZOA Anniversary Convocation, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Convention- ZOA, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Annual Meeting, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- AZF Kickoff, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- AZF Seating, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Israel Tours, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Israel Tourist Information, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- AZF Lists, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Contracts, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Purim Dance, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Purim Dance, Miscellaneous, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Program Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Speakers, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Program Data, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Publicity, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Synagogue Relations, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Regional Reports: Akron, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Regional Reports: Aliquippa, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Regional Reports: Altoona, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Regional Reports: Beaver Falls, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Regional Reports: Brownsville, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Regional Reports: Butler, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Regional Reports: Canonsburg, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Regional Reports: Canton, Ohio, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Regional Reports: Charleston, W. Va, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 9)